<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>¿Quienes somos? on </title>
    <link>https://entotechsolution.com/en/equipo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ¿Quienes somos? on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 10:01:52 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://entotechsolution.com/en/equipo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Roca</title>
      <link>https://entotechsolution.com/en/equipo/xavi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 09:58:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://entotechsolution.com/en/equipo/xavi/</guid>
      <description>Veterinaria - UAB&#xA;Master en producción animal y cienciade los alimentos - UAB&#xA;Gran experiencia técnica en el área dela producción y nutrición animal y losprocesos industriales, sobre todo en larecuperación, reaprovechamiento yreciclaje de alimentos para laalimentación animal. Colaborador enproyectos de I+D+I tanto europeos(INNOPROTEIN 2021) como nacionales(NATURDEV 2019).&#xA;Con ello, Xavier aporta una visión técnica y rigurosa en el desarrollo delproyecto, lo que permitirá laelaboración de productos de altacalidad y cumpliendo con los más altosestándares de seguridad alimentaria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordi Cassany</title>
      <link>https://entotechsolution.com/en/equipo/jordi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 09:58:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://entotechsolution.com/en/equipo/jordi/</guid>
      <description>ADE - UNAV&#xA;EMBA - IESE Business School&#xA;Experiencia profesional en el área deEstrategia en EY y responsable de Estrategia en Equatorial Coca-Cola, lebrinda una perspectiva única en lagestión de proyectos empresariales yen la comprensión de loscomportamientos del mercado.&#xA;Con ello, la presencia de Jordi comoadvisor del proyecto aportaráexperiencia y conocimientos y unavisión estratégica, financiera yempresarial clave para la toma&#xA;Xavier Roca&#xD;Jose&#xD;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jose</title>
      <link>https://entotechsolution.com/en/equipo/jose/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 09:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://entotechsolution.com/en/equipo/jose/</guid>
      <description>Drinking 1-1 glass of green tea (lemon grass) every morning, afternoon and evening helps to reduce joint pain. Boiled milk, sugar can be added if desired. Cinnamon powder taken with 1-1 teaspoon of honey every morning and evening for many days relieves joint pain. Consuming as much cauliflower as possible in daily meals relieves joint pain. Joint pain is caused by defects in the blood and urine, which can be avoided by eating cauliflower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Roca</title>
      <link>https://entotechsolution.com/en/equipo/david/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 09:55:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://entotechsolution.com/en/equipo/david/</guid>
      <description>Take 10 ml (2 teaspoons) of sesame oil and warm it a little. By pulling oil from this oil, i.e. keeping it in the mouth, turn it for 10 to 15 minutes and then spit it out. . Another experiment is from sesame oil. Sesame oil is used to massage the throat. This massage is to be done below or above the neck, keep doing this massage for five minutes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
